let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is -",
    answer: "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
    options: [
      "Head, Title, HTML, body",
      "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
      "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
      "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question:"Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?",
    answer: "b",
    options: [
      "p",
      "b",
      "br",
      "pre"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Which of the following tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?",
    answer: "h1",
    options: [
      "h6",
      "h7",
      "h1",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How to create an unordered list (a list with the list items in bullets) in HTML?",
    answer: "ul",
    options: [
      "ul",
      "ol",
      "li",
      "i"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which character is used to represent the closing of a tag in HTML?",
    answer: "/",
    options: [
      "/",
      ".",
      "none",
      "!"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many types of tags are present in HTML",
    answer: "2 types",
   options: [
      "2 types",
      "1 type",
      "3 types",
      "4 types"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the difference between an opening tag and a closing tag?",
    answer: "Closing tag has a / back.",
   options: [
      "Opening tag has a / in front.",
      "Closing tag has a / in front.",
      "There is no difference.",
      "Closing tag has a / back."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "< br/> What type of tag is this?",
    answer: "break tag",
   options: [
      "break tag",
      "A broken one",
      "An opening tag",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Where do all items for the same website need to be saved?",
    answer: "In the same folder",
   options: [
      "In the same folder",
      "A broken one",
      "An opening tag",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many number of heading tags are present?",
    answer: "6",
   options: [
      "2",
      "3",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  }
];
